FWD Singapore began as a market
disrupter and strive to change the way
you feel about Insurance 3 is on this is
what we've succeeded in changing buying
is now easier
no more Agent P sucks when you can now
get your life insurance cover in less
than 50 minutes
directly online getting a quote for your
car insurance used to take twenty nine
questions but now it's just ten claims
are made easier submitting claims used
to be a hassle
not anymore just submit your claim
online for any of our products no more
forms required for travel insurance no
payments is required at panel clinics
just flash your medical ecard in the FWD
flyer app we're about payments waiting
for checks took up to five days FWD
customers get paid instantly by pay now
direct into their bank accounts we paid
out over million claims a whopping
ninety eight percent of all claims
process our products are made different
to better support you FWD s only insurer
to provide cashless outpatient medical
expenses for your helper we cover all
types and stages of cancer and payout
100% of your summer shirt while
international health insurance provides
you with medical coverage no matter
where you are we are also the only
insurer to offer NCD for life to our
motorists customers as well as the first
to introduce a packaged employee
benefits plan that reduces duplications
between integrated shield plans and
group insurance FWD synergy companies
can now save more while employees get to
receive daily cash benefits if they are
hospitalized
if you
a letter of guarantee as a customer of
our group policy it will be done online
to keep adding another to our
achievement list FWD is now the
appointed insurer for HTV fire insurance
we are always here for you
faith chatbot is at your service 24/7
now also available on Google home and
Google Voice our emergency assistance
also operates 24/7 FWD is well loved by
our customers over three hundred and
three thousand of them leave one of the
highest renewal rates in the industry a
Trustpilot score of nine point one out
of ten from ensuring the welfare of an
individual to hundreds of thousands of
employees thank you for making it
possible